daype.com 2010-06-22

# Privacy Policy | Daype Online Free Classifieds

This Privacy Policy describes how Daype, Inc. (referred to as "Daype") collects, protects and uses your Personal Information. This Privacy Policy applies to Daype's web site located at www.daype.com (the "Site"). By using the Site, you consent to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If there is a conflict between Daype's Terms of Use governing your use of the Site and this Privacy Policy, the Terms of Use control.� This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time.� Any such updated version of this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon posting to the Site. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy each time you use the Site to ensure you understand the terms applicable to you as a result of such use.

Personal Information

In various places on the Site, Daype may collect "Personal Information", such as your name, e-mail address, or other information that can be used to identify you or contact you. Daype will not share any of your Personal Information, except for the information you choose to publicly disclose in the ads you post. Daype offers email anonymization and relay to protect your identity and reduce spam.

Account information is password protected. Keep your password safe. Daype does not knowingly collect any Personal Information from persons under the age of 18, and Daype does not permit persons under the age of 18 to register on the Site.

Daype, or users that place ads on Daype, may provide links to third party web sites, which may have different privacy practices than Daype. Daype is not responsible for, nor has any control over, the privacy policies on these third party web sites.

Security

Although Daype works hard to protect your Personal Information, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your Personal Information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we do our best to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your Personal Information or private communications will always remain private, and you acknowledge and agree that Daype will have no liability to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss or misuse.

Archiving and Display of Postings by Search Engines and Other Sites

You acknowledge that search engines and other sites not affiliated with Daype including, among others, archive.org, google.com, and groups.yahoo.com may archive or otherwise make available the content of the SIte. If you remove or modify your content on the Site, there is a possibility one of these sites may provide access to old or deleted content. Daype is not responsible in any way for any display of such content by these third party sites.

Cookies

When you visit the Site, you will be assigned a "cookie" (a small text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of this cookie is to identify you when you visit the Site so that Daype can enhance its service.

You can choose to browse the Site without cookies, but that will limit your ability to take advantage of certain features of the Site.

No Spam

You are not licensed to add other users of the Site, even a user who has purchased an item from you, to your mailing list (email or physical mail) without their express consent. You may not use Daype's communication tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate Daype's Terms of Use.

Information Disclosure

By using the Site you acknowledge and agree that Daype may, in its sole discretion, preserve or disclose your personal information as well as IP addresses, timestamps, and other user information, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such preservation or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with a legal process; (b) enforce Daype's Terms of Use; (c) respond to claims that any content of the Site violates the rights of third-parties; (d) respond to claims that contact information of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; (e) protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Daype, its users or the general public.

This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 8, 2008.
